{
    "id": "7f40ce86c22243e486a6812fa586dadd",
    "title": "Identify the noun clause",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "76b29010a4ca44bdabca876acfb683d4",
            "title": "Noun Clauses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "............................... he said is of no importance to me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "That",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The king said ..................................... his minister deserved to be honored.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "how"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The news ................................. all was well delighted everyone.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "how",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is interesting to notice ...................................... soon birds learn the danger of electric wires.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "how",
                        "why",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The bench of judges declared .................................... the accused was not guilty.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "how"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The report ..................................... only ten persons were killed in the explosion is not true.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "that",
                        "how"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I want to know ..................................... far the station is from here.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "how",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is strongly rumored ...................................... plague has broken out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "why"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said ...................................... his sister was ill.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "how"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is strange ...................................... you should think so.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "that",
                        "how"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}